# **Adam Kisorsi**

# Front End Developer

Front End Developer with more than five years of experience working with JavaScript, HTML/CSS and FE frameworks to deliver exceptional customer experiences. Adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining customer satisfaction.

Barcelona, Spain +36 30 652 9697 kisorsiadam@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/adam-kisorsi

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Luxoft, Barcelona Senior Frontend Developer

#### February 2023 -

- Led the development of high-quality, scalable, and maintainable crowdsourcing platform.
- Conducted code reviews and mentored junior developers to ensure code quality and best practices.
- Collaborated closely with the product team, the backend team and UX/UI designers to refine project requirements and deliver an exceptional user experience.

### Appwise Zrt, Budapest

## Frontend Developer

### September 2018 - February 2023

- Participated in each step of the product development process from ideation to development in a resource planner manager.
- Participating in the development of the ticket sale website. It's the most used transportation ticket sale application in Hungary. Using Angular Material to build responsive and accessible user interfaces that comply with WCAG and other web accessibility standards.
- Participating in the improvement of the package logistic application and road error mapping application.
- Contributed to the development of company-wide coding standards, best practices, and guidelines for Angular development.
- Participated in the development of a road error mapping application.
- All the projects mentioned above were made with the most current version of Angular

## Eclectiqminds, Budapest

#### Frontend Developer

#### March 2017 - September 2018 (part time)

- Developed a ticket sale website for Veszprem Zoo.
- Maintained a bank independent financial application.
- Developed a highly stable and easy to use web application for the biggest arena in Hungary. Among others it contains a ticket mirror editor, entrance gates and BLEs handler, catering packages manager.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5 CSS3, SASS Javascript, Typescript RxJS, NgRx Jasmine, Karma, Jest Module Federation

Angular, Vue GatsbyJS

PostgreSQL, REST, GraphQL

Prismic WordPress

Git

Azure, Jenkins, Docker

UX, UI

Figma, Balsamiq, Adobe XD

#### **EDUCATION**

# Corvinus University of Budapest

IT

2017

**Budapest** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Hungarian

#### **SIDE PROJECTS**

Touchbud
Underseawear.com
Zollhof.de
Webshops
Smaller sites

# Nokia, Budapest

# Web Developer

May 2016 - March 2017 (part time)

- Optimized and created user-friendly internal tools instead of obsolete ones.
- Developed a new internal tool which helps the interns to easily get to know the daily used tools.